Corinne Bradford

linkedin.com/in/cori-bradford github.com/coribradford

Software Engineering Intern

Upcoming graduate offering a strong foundation in software engineering and programming fundamentals across multiple platforms. Experienced in object-oriented programming, developing, testing, and debugging code. Utilizes interpersonal skills to consult with internal and external clients to ensure end-user satisfaction. Quick learner with an aptitude for mastering new technologies and a demonstrated ability to work both independently and in a team.

Education

B.S. Computer Science Software Engineering - Oregon State University - Cascades

Dec 2022

Academic Honors: 3.72 GPA, Dean's List (3 Terms), Tau Beta Pi Honor Society

Bend, Oregon

Relevant Coursework:

- Software Engineering
- Software Development
- Business of Software
- Data Structures

- Analysis of Algorithms
- Network Security
- Machine Learning & Data Mining
- Cloud Application Development

Technical Skills

Python	C/C++	MySQL
Ruby	Java	Postgres
JavaScript	Rails	Git

Experience

Student Project Consultant, OSU-Cascades Innovation Co-Lab - Bend, Oregon

Dec 2021-Present

• Consult with internal and external clients on Software Development projects

Student Software Developer, OSU-Cascades - Bend, Oregon

Sept 2021—Present

Ecotone Capstone Team

- Utilized interpersonal skills to coordinate with a team of 4 in the process of updating libraries and functionality in a legacy application.
- Assist team in ongoing development and testing of new features

Student Teaching Assistant, OSU-Cascades - Bend, Oregon

Jan 2021-Dec 2021

- Debugged, tested, and assessed Python and Java programming assignments for classes of 30+ students
- Conducted weekly study groups, explained concepts and assisted in labs, projects, and other related materials

Student Research Assistant, OSU-Cascades - Bend, Oregon

Jan 2021-Oct 2021

- Research project to construct a smart dog collar using a microcontroller and sensors
- Utilized data collected from prototypes and Machine Learning algorithms to detect and correctly identify seizures in canines